

PROFILE

Bakery and pastry, experiences for 10+ years on procurement, HR, sales, distribution, Istanbul, Turkey. 1,5-year experience on construction of warehouse project oversight, Istanbul, Turkey.

4 years management experience on importation and distribution of supermarket items, Kigali, Rwanda.

I am a natural, realistic, flexible, polite, and cooperative person. I am capable to work with in a team or single. I believe continuation of lifelong learning; accordingly, I am open to learn new skills. Currently I am studying for a bachelor's degree in Machine Learning and Data Engineering at Lapland UAS.

CONTACT

PHONE:

+358 44910 2296

EMAIL

ali.ozaydin@edu.lapinamk.fi

HOBBIES

Creating small applications via Python. Fixing, damaged or broken personal belongings.

ALI ÖZAYDIN

EDUCATION

University of Sakarya, B.B.A

2001 - 2005

Istanbul Commerce University, INT. TRADE, M.A 2007 - 2008

Lapland UAS, Machine Learning and Data Engineering, B.S.E

WORK EXPERIENCE

PARPALANDIA OY Office Organizer, Tourism

2022/12 - 2023/3

Customer service for tourists and email communications.

MAHLAS LTD Managing Director, Importation

2016-2020

Managed procurement. Coordinated logistics and transports. Performed financial transactions. Established employees' customer visit tracking system and managed route plans as well as visit performance via applications. Through it, delivery system strengthened, and sales were increased.

ÖZSA CONSTRUCTION Supervisor, Warehouse Construction

2013-2014

Over sought the construction project from starting up to ending. Calculated the payments with the site supervisor and sub-contractor for the completed parts.

ÖZSA & ÖZAYDIN UNLU LTD Bakery and Pastry

2001-2014

Performed sales, procurement, customer service, banking, and accounting activities.

SKILLS KEYWORDS

Communication	# Python	# Data Analytics
Problem solving	# Freight forwarding	# HTML
Math	# Finance	# JavaScript
Finnish B1 level	# Procurement	# CSS
English	# Multi-culture	# MySql